<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2016 The Android Open Source Project
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->
<resources>
    <string-array name="places">
        <item>Be an Auto Rider</item>
        <item>Be a Cab Rider</item>
        <item>Create a Ride</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="place_desc">
        <item>Find an Auto helps you to find other Autos that</item>
        <item>Find a Cab helps you to find other Cabs that</item>
        <item>Create a Ride Helps you to create rides that other users can find</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="place_details">
        <item>Be an auto rider helps you find other riders nearby that have created an auto ride and are going to the same destination as you.
            This helps you save some money every time you ride an auto. Also
            since charges on services like Ola Auto and Jugnoo are much less
            compared to conventional autos run by auto unions there is a big
            difference in the amount you need to pay using this service.
        </item>
        <item>
            Be a cab rider helps you find other riders nearby that have
            created a cab ride and are going to the same destination as you.
            This helps you save some money every time you ride an cab. Cabs
            are usually very costly when taken alone but with the help of rider you can find
            other people who wish to go to the same destination. Thus you can sit easily in
            comfort and enjoy the AC in the cab. Sit back and be a Rider.
        </item>
        <item>Create a ride helps you create a cab or an auto ride whichever you prefer.
            Other Riders nearby who also wish to go to same place can contact you via the app
            and you dont need to share your personal information such as phone number or email with
            strangers. Once you create a ride other users can instantly find your ride and contact
            you via the app.
        </item>


    </string-array>
    <string-array name="place_locations">
        <item>Amity University \n(we currently support only this location.
        Other places might be added in the future versions)</item>
        <item>Amity University \n(we currently support only this location.
        Other places might be added in the future versions)</item>
        <item>Amity University \n(we currently support only this location.
        Other places might be added in the future versions)</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="places_picture">
        <item>@drawable/a</item>
        <item>@drawable/b</item>
        <item>@drawable/c</item>
    </array>
</resources>
